{
	"cards": [
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-31-tag-vocabulary-card-1",
			"front": "An injury in which there is soft-tissue damage inside the body but the skin remains intact.",
			"back": "closed abdominal injury"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-31-tag-vocabulary-card-2",
			"front": "The displacement of organs outside of the body.",
			"back": "evisceration"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-31-tag-vocabulary-card-3",
			"front": "The region below the rib cage and above the hip.",
			"back": "flank"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-31-tag-vocabulary-card-4",
			"front": "Involuntary muscle contractions (spasm) of the abdominal wall to minimize the pain of abdominal movement; a sign of peritonitis.",
			"back": "guarding"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-31-tag-vocabulary-card-5",
			"front": "Blood in the urine.",
			"back": "hematuria"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-31-tag-vocabulary-card-6",
			"front": "Structures through which materials pass, such as the stomach, small intestines, large intestines, ureters, and urinary bladder.",
			"back": "hollow organs"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-31-tag-vocabulary-card-7",
			"front": "Black, foul-smelling, tarry stool containing digested blood.",
			"back": "melena"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-31-tag-vocabulary-card-8",
			"front": "An injury in which there is a break in the surface of the skin or mucous membrane, exposing deeper tissue to potential contamination.",
			"back": "open abdominal injury"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-31-tag-vocabulary-card-9",
			"front": "The abdominal cavity.",
			"back": "peritoneal cavity"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-31-tag-vocabulary-card-10",
			"front": "The membrane lining the abdominal cavity (parietal) and covering the abdominal organs (visceral).",
			"back": "peritoneum"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-31-tag-vocabulary-card-11",
			"front": "The potential space located posterior to the peritoneal cavity of the abdomen.",
			"back": "retroperitoneum"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-31-tag-vocabulary-card-12",
			"front": "Solid masses of tissue where much of the chemical work of the body takes place (eg, the liver, spleen, pancreas, and kidneys).",
			"back": "solid organs"
		}
	],
	"category": {
		"value": "chapter-31",
		"label": "Chapter 31"
	},
	"tags": [
		{
			"value": "vocabulary",
			"label": "Vocabulary"
		}
	]
}